{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [{ "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "How does exercise help in managing your diet?", "correct_answer": "Helps regulate my metabolism so I have a health appetite", "incorrect_answers": ["Makes me want to eat less", "Makes me lose weight", "Makes me drink more so I eat less"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "A simple workout can effect your productivity:", "correct_answer": "Give me a natural energy boost", "incorrect_answers": ["Give me strength to do more intensive tasks", "Make me more competitive with others", "Make me feel more confident"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What hormones make us happy after we exercise?", "correct_answer": "endorphins", "incorrect_answers": ["testosterones", "prostoglandins", "thyroxin"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What is CBT an acronym for?", "correct_answer": "Cognitive Behavioural Therapy", "incorrect_answers": ["Change By Thought", "Careful But Thorough", "Call Back Today"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Psychologists in London claim they have cracked the code on the ideal embrace, saying hugs should last between: (countryliving.com)", "correct_answer": "five and 10 seconds", "incorrect_answers": ["2 and 5 minutes", "1 and 2 minutes", "10 to 15 minutes"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Why does having a pet make a difference to your mood?", "correct_answer": "Pets can help manage loneliness and depression by giving us companionship", "incorrect_answers": ["Make us get out to buy their food", "We can talk to others about them", "We can meet others with pets when in the park"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "How many glasses of water/liquid a day should we have?", "correct_answer": "6 to 8", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "2 to 3", "4 to 6"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What does water help with:", "correct_answer": "Less dehydration more clear thinking", "incorrect_answers": ["Visiting the toilet more", "More fatigue", "Increasing blood pressure"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "How important is diet in effecting our moods?", "correct_answer": "Blood sugar fluctuations can effect our moods", "incorrect_answers": ["Eating whatever we want makes me feel happy", "Getting the correct nutrients makes my body work better so I'm happier", "Not eating much makes me feel less worried about how I look"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What happens when we don't eat?", "correct_answer": "The body begins to increase production of cortisol, leaving us stressed and hangry", "incorrect_answers": ["We lose weight", "We make up for it later by over-eating", "We get dehydrated quickly and therefore need to drink more water to compensate"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What activity does not lead to improved mood, if you can't do regular exercise?", "correct_answer": "Watching TV", "incorrect_answers": ["Floating in a pool", "Sitting in a park", "Playing with your pet"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What is mindfulness?", "correct_answer": "Having an awareness of feelings, bodily sensations, and surrounding environment moment by moment", "incorrect_answers": ["Being thoughtful of others and offering to help them", "Being conscious of our surroundings and the events that effect them", "Having a friend check in with us to be mindful of the difficulties we are going through"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Why are having goals important?", "correct_answer": "It helps us to look forward rather than in our past", "incorrect_answers": ["Gives us a holiday to plan for", "Helps us score points at football/rugby/hockey", "Stops us kicking the ball all over the field and into the crowds"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "How does vitamin D boost our wellbeing?", "correct_answer": "Increases Serotonin, fights depression and increases happiness", "incorrect_answers": ["Makes us get less ill as helps improve the immune system", "Prevents Rickets", "Helps us get a tan when sitting in the sun"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Why is sleep so important to our wellbeing?", "correct_answer": "It helps us process emotional information so we can regulate", "incorrect_answers": ["It gives us rest so we can reset and start another day", "It lets us have time to dream and this helps us escape from reality", "It decreases fatigue so we can have energy to interact with others in the day"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What happens when we don't get enough sleep?", "correct_answer": "Lack of sleep can effect our immune systems and lead to frequent illness", "incorrect_answers": ["Lack of sleep can lead to being less alert and falling asleep while watching tv", "We slur our words when we haven't had enough sleep and people don't understand us", "Lack of sleep can lead to less patience and get angry quickly leading to outbursts"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What is emotional regulation?", "correct_answer": "Being in control of your emotions so that you don't become overwhelmed", "incorrect_answers": ["Rules about emotions that have to be upheld", "Expressing your emotions in a safe place", "Knowing when to express your emotions and the appropriate way"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What effect does sitting in the sunshine have?", "correct_answer": "It increases vitamin D production", "incorrect_answers": ["It gives us cancer", "It makes us hot", "It helps us get a tan"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What is melatonin vs melanin?", "correct_answer": "Melatonin is a sleep hormone, Melanin is a pigment that helps our skin darken in the sun", "incorrect_answers": ["Melatonin is what is released to darken our skin in the sun, Melanin is a sleep hormone", "Melanin breaks down Melatonin, so that our bodies can absorb vitamin D from the sun", "Melanin is a type of plastic that is used for plates and cups, Melatonin is an exercise to help us tone our muscles"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "How does Boxing physically help our moods?", "correct_answer": "We release endorphins when we exercise so that helps improve our mood", "incorrect_answers": ["We can pretend we are hitting the person we don't like", "We have a sparring partner so we can interact socially too", "We test our own limits and gain confidence"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "When you have a difficult task, what can you plan to look forward to,  motivate you to achieve it?", "correct_answer": "A reward to look forward to when completed", "incorrect_answers": ["A to do list", "A break in-between things", "A chat with a friend"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "How many units of alcohol should you have a week to help improve your wellbeing?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "4", "10"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Does caffeine help with anxiety? Why?", "correct_answer": "No, it stimulates fight or flight response and can make anxiety worse", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes, it helps me move faster", "No, it makes my heart race and I feel more panicky", "Yes, it moves the hormones around by body faster so I calm down quicker"] }, { "category": "Wellbeing", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "What tea can help reduce anxiety and aid with restful sleep?", "correct_answer": "Camomile tea", "incorrect_answers": ["Regular tea", "Mint tea", "Green tea"] }]
}